Let's see. Sperm meets egg here.
Um, 30 days has September.
All the rest have 31.
Except for Judith, who has 28.
Hey, Alan. Meet Don.
- Hello, Don.
- Hello, Alan.
Don drove me home
and I don't have any money.
Okay. Uh, is Don a cabbie?
No. No. Don is a close personal friend.
Don is a cabbie, he has enough friends...
...and he wants his $80.
- What happened to your money?
- Good question.
You know how easy
Texas Hold'em looks on TV...
...when you can see
the other guys' hole cards?
- Yeah.
- Very different in real life.
Uh, 20, 40, 60, 80.
No tip?
Hold on.
Let me see. Five dollar-
Keep you money, Mr. Trump.
You need it more than I do.
Are we still on for lunch?
I think you offended Don.
He'll get over it. Where's your car?
Don't change the subject.
You owe Don an apology.
- Oh, hey, a calendar.
- Yeah.
- What's "JMC" stand for?
- Nothing.
Oh, come on. John Mellencamp Cougar?
No.
Jumping Methodist Cougar?
- No.
- Then I give up.
Well, if you must know,
it stands for "Judith's menstrual cycle."
- Get out.
- No, look.
This is when Judith and Herb broke up.
And this is the day
that I had sex with her.
Dude, you need a better hobby.
Judith is now five months pregnant.
Oh, yeah, right.
She's probably in that sweet spot
where her boobs are big and cushy...
...but her ass is still normal.
Charlie, it is almost certain
that I am the father of Judith's baby.
Are you still grinding on this?
What if it's a girl?
I always wanted a daughter.
I finally get one
and some other guy gets to be her dad.
I feel like the universe is playing
some horrible practical joke on me.
Wow, I lost $8000 playing poker...
...have no idea where my car is...
...threw up in my mouth three times...
...and I'm still having a better night
than you are.
I don't expect you to understand.
You don't know the joy
of being a parent.
Of watching a part of you
grow and develop...
...blooming into a fully-formed
human being.
Four times.
- Hi.
Jake, your father's here.
- So how you doing?
- Good.
- Over the morning sickness?
- Yes, Alan.
Uh, by my calculations
probably about a week, 10 days ago.
- That sounds right.
- Good, good.
You have a nice break
till the, uh, old hemorrhoids come a-calling.
Jake!
Judith, are we gonna talk about
the elephant in the room?
- What elephant?
- Come on, you, me, the baby?
- We did have unprotected sex when-
- You shut your mouth. We did not.
- Yes, we did.
- Read my lips. We did not have sex.
- Oh, hey, Alan. How goes it?
- Oh, uh, fine, Herb.
- How you doing?
- Proud as a peacock.
- Honey, did you show him the sonogram?
- No.
Oh, you should see her, Alan.
Her? So it is a girl?
Yep. One fresh-faced little fetus
sans wee-wee.
I always wanted a "sans wee-wee."
Well, you can't have mine.
No, no, of course not.
- Hey, wanna see the nursery?
- He doesn't wanna see the nursery.
Sure. You going with mermaids?
Girls love mermaids.
Oh, actually, I was thinking little ponies.
- Little ponies?
- Yeah. Why?
Oh, gosh. Little ponies have little penises.
Really?
I didn't notice that on the stencils.
Let's go take a look.
- I'm ready.
- Oh, uh, I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna go see the baby's room.
- He never wants to see my room.
- That's because your room is a pig sty.
I didn't ask for a reason.
Alan, buddy, I'm getting a little concerned
about your drinking.
I don't have a problem.
Well, I do. You're swilling my good stuff.
Here.
Have some Old Walmart.
Thank you.
What's this?
Uh, a diary I kept
during Judith's pregnancy.
"Jennifer, Jocelyn, Jasmine, Jolene"?
Some of the names that we picked out
in case Jake had been a girl.
Oh, man.
Can you imagine him as a chick?
Woof.
Yeah, well, that's not how it turned out.
Think about it, though.
Every weekend, me, you
and a big ugly girl with a bad haircut.
- I'm gonna have a daughter, Charlie.
- Okay, okay.
First of all, you don't know it's your kid.
All we know is that when Judith and Herb
broke up, you nailed Judith.
Then when they reconciled,
Herb nailed Judith.
So the only thing we know for sure
is that, despite all outward appearances...
...Judith is a slut.
Hey, I'm aware that technically
either one of us could be the father...
...but I know in my gut
that this is my sweet bastard child.
You don't know squat.
You wanna talk technically?
Technically,
maybe neither one of you is the father.
Oh, dear God, Charlie.
What have you done?
Not me, you fool. Although if I'd known
she was that easy, maybe-
Stop.
I'm saying is there could very well
be some guy in her driveway...
...with a leaf blower pining away
for baby Juanita.
That's just ridiculous.
Judith won't even eat Mexican food.
Look, look.
Even if you're right, doing anything about it
is just gonna destroy a marriage.
I know. I know. It's just so hard
to ignore my paternal instincts.
Sure, I see those instincts with Jake
and I admire them.
I would've dropped him off
at an orphanage...
...with 20 bucks and a bag of doughnuts.
No, you wouldn't.
He was adorable when he was a baby.
Baby? I'm talking about last week.
I walked into his room,
he was trying to bite his toenails.
Let's be honest, that's monkey behavior.
My son is not a monkey.
My point here is forget the baby.
You've already got a kid to raise.
Yeah, I guess.
Hi.
He's not a monkey.
- did a good job
upfront and he had a ton of-
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
- I don't wanna watch football.
- Nobody cares what you wanna watch.
Why do you get to decide everything?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe it's because
I bought everything around here.
Oh, right, play the money card.
That's all you got.
That's all I need. Now shut up.
No, you shut up.
All right, I'm gonna count to three
and then I'm gonna kick your ass.
Ooh, I'm scared.
One.
- Two.
- I'm only leaving because I'm bored.
He keeps growing, I'm screwed.
Hey, uh, you wanna hear
what I wrote the night you were born?
Not really.
Oh, come on. Come on, uh, sit down.
You'll like it.
It's kind of a poem, heh. Um...
My son, my son, my only one
You open my heart like the morning sun
Your tiny face, your tiny hand
Never have I felt a love so grand
Gay.
What do you know about poetry,
you monkey?
Oh, hey, Herb.
Thought I'd stop by and see if you need
any help with the baby's room.
- Thanks. I'm painting today.
- Oh, great.
Just call me Vincent van Gogh-ing
to help you.
Funnier in my head. Let's go.
Oh, look who stopped by
to help paint the baby's room.
- Surprise.
- Herb doesn't need any help, Alan.
- Yes, I do.
- Yes, he does.
Come on, I'm just gonna start
on the unicorn stencils.
Unicorns? Oh, Herb,
that's just a pony with a strap-on.
I know, tell me about it.
It's like nine kinds of suck
in an eight-suck bag.
- Hey, Jake?
- Gotta go.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
Yeah, well, you should have thought of that
before you barged in.
Yeah.
The reason I barged in...
...was to apologize for threatening
to kick your ass.
I wouldn't really do that.
You couldn't really do that.
Anyway, I was thinking about
ordering a pizza. You interested?
No, thanks.
Maybe you didn't hear me. Pizza.
Dough, sauce, cheese, grease, meat.
I've seen you lick the box.
I'm not hungry.
- Okay, what the hell's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
Fine. Be that way.
I know what's going on here.
You're bent out of shape
because your mom's having a baby.
- No, I'm not.
- It's okay. Nothing to be ashamed of.
In fact, I know exactly how you feel.
My mom's second child ruined my life.
- That's my dad.
- Uh-huh.
But listen, it wasn't all bad.
When babies grow up a little,
you can have fun with them.
You know, pee in their canteen,
teach them to stutter.
The down side is they're so damaged...
...later on they move into your guest room
with their kid and never leave.
Not that I don't love having you here.
You're a delight.
- I'm fine with the baby.
- Really?
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
Well, that's a novel approach.
So if it's not the baby, then why have you
been such a dillweed lately?
- None of your business.
- So it's a girl.
- Just get out of my room.
- Make me.
God, you're such a child.
Oh, yeah, it's a girl.
- Hmm. Jolene.
- Yeah.
Jolene Melnick.
- Nope, I don't think so.
- Why not? You could call her Jo or Josie.
Kind of wanted to name her
after my grandma Mildred.
- Mildred Melnick?
- Yeah. We could call her Mil or Millie.
I'm sorry, Herb.
With a name like Mildred you might as well
call her Staff Sergeant Melnick.
- Herb, can you get the cookies for me?
- Oh, sure.
We, uh, keep them on the top shelf
of the pantry. You know, Jake.
Yeah. Charlie keeps his fudge nuggets
in the trunk of his car.
Thank you, dear.
What are you doing here?
I'm helping my friend. Helping you.
If not for me, our little girl would be
surrounded by metaphorical pony peni.
Our little girl? I don't know what you
imagine happened between you and me...
...but if you say anything to Herb,
I'll put a gun in your mouth...
...and paint these walls with your brains.
I think we settled on mermaids.
Cookie for my cookie?
Oh, yum. Thank you.
- Wow, pregnancy's a wild ride, huh?
- Ugh.
One minute she's loving and affectionate
and the next minute she's, well-
Cruel? Vengeful? Castrating?
I was gonna say "moody."
Wait for it.
Of course I wanna go to the party.
Because my stupid uncle won't let me.
I don't know,
because he's old and clueless.
No, I can't sneak out.
I gotta be here to change his adult diapers.
Otherwise, he just sits in his own filth.
I know, it's really gross.
- Hi there.
- Gotta go.
You're not supposed to listen
to my private conversations.
You're not supposed to tell people
I crap my pants.
Okay, whatever.
What's the deal with this party
I'm supposedly not letting you go to...
...like I give a rat's ass
about your social life.
Just leave me alone.
You know that's not gonna happen.
Come on, you can trust me.
You told me
"Never trust a guy who says 'Trust me. "'
Did you trust me when I told you that?
Um, I'm confused.
Now tell me why
you don't wanna go to this party.
- I can't tell you. It's embarrassing.
- Okay, okay.
How about I tell you something
embarrassing about myself first?
Like what?
Well, let's see.
All right.
About 15 years ago, I was in Bangkok.
- What?
- Bangkok.
- It's a real place, you nimrod.
- Still funny, though.
Anyway, I was in this bar
and I met this beautiful woman...
...and I was a little drunk
and I didn't notice the Adam's apple.
But later that night-
Well, believe me,
I was really embarrassed.
Girls don't have Adam's apples.
Oh, dude. You are such a 'mo.
- No, no, no. We just kissed.
- Aw, that's even worse.
- All right. I shared, now you share.
- You didn't have to share that.
A fart in the lunch line
would've made your point.
I get it. I'm sorry. Now talk.
Okay.
Well, there's this girl I kind of like
and she's gonna be at the party tonight.
Uh-huh.
And she said she wants
to hook up with me.
And you're nervous.
Well, she's gone out with a ninth grader
and she's done stuff.
Okay, I get it.
You've got yourself an experienced
older woman who knows more.
Everybody knows more than me.
You should hear the things
my friends have done.
- Oh, please. How old are your friends?
- Same age as me.
- How old are you?
- Fourteen.
Hmm, horrible age.
All right, first of all...
...whenever 14-year-old boys talk
about sex, they're lying.
But for a guy like you,
the truth can be a powerful tool.
- What?
- Powerful tool.
Stay with me, Jake.
How about a powerful tool in Bangkok?
Jake, what I'm trying to tell you here
is that the truth can work for you.
That I don't know what I'm doing?
Yep, play to your strengths.
Which in your case is ignorance.
Here, I'll show you.
You gently cup her face in your hands,
look her in the eye and tell her:
"I'm new at this and I'm trusting you
to be patient with me."
You're kidding.
Nope. Girls eat that crap up.
And I'll tell you something else, that line
will work for you all through college.
Or in your case,
your second hitch in the Navy.
Go get dressed
and I'll take you to that party.
- Thanks, Uncle Charlie.
- No problem, buddy.
Still didn't need to hear
that Bangkok story.
I'm sorry.
It's gonna give me nightmares.
Welcome to the club.
All right, we're agreed on a Montessori
preschool, but what about child care?
Oh, well, uh, Judith's mother has told us
we can count on her for babysitting.
Ooh.
- What?
- Oh, nothing. Lenore is a lovely woman.
- I'm sure the baby will be fine.
- Oh, okay, good.
Yeah, she's probably got a lid
on those demons by now.
- What demons?
- Oh, ah, well, it's no biggie.
Um, she just, uh, had a little rough patch
with the prescription pills.
The intervention, the rehab.
- There was an intervention?
- And rehab. Um, three times.
- Three times?
- Well, so far. Um...
Oh, dear God, what the hell happened?
Golly, I didn't wanna be the one
to tell you.
Alan, please.
All right. Um...
Lenore was babysitting one night,
and when Judith and I came home...
...we found her face down in a bowl
of H墧en-Dazs with Percocets in her hair.
- You're kidding.
- Oh, that's not the scary part.
Um, we heard some shrieking
and, uh, found baby Jake...
...with his head stuck in a doggie door
trying to fend off a raccoon.
- A raccoon?
- Yeah. Yeah.
We got him all the shots, uh,
just to be safe...
...but he was never the same after that.
- Judith never told me about this.
- Well, it's her mother, Herb.
I mean, what's she gonna say?
But tell you what,
sneak up on Jake one night...
...wearing a Davy Crockett hat
and see what happens.
Anyway, uh, if you ever need a sitter
for little Jolene...
...you, uh, you call Uncle Alan.
- How's it going in here?
- Oh, honey. Good news.
Alan's offered to babysit
so we don't have risk calling your mother.
JUDITH:
Get out!
A raccoon? And you believed him?
Are you insane?
How do I look?
- She already likes you, right?
- Yeah.
Then you look great.
Let's go.
- Hello?
- Oh.
I'm still not real sure about this.
What's the big deal?
I told you how to handle it.
I know. I just-
I just don't wanna go.
All right.
No hurry.
It's not like they're gonna stop
making girls.
Hey.
How about we order that pizza
and watch a movie?
Cool. I should probably change back
into my eating shirt.
Don't worry. You can't ruin this shirt.
What the hell is that cologne?
Air freshener from the toilet.
I figured I was spraying it anyway.
Oh, hey, Judith. What's up?
Actually, quite a bit.
- Is something wrong?
- No, uh, it's just, um...
- I think it's time you knew the truth.
- What truth?
Marlene Melnick is your daughter.
I knew it.
For 14 years, I've known it.
Well, I told her everything
and she wants to live with her real dad.
That's great.
It's okay, honey. Come on in.
Hi, Daddy.
You got anything to eat?
Woof.